John V. Dowdy, Sr. papers, Inclusive: 1926-1986, undated; Bulk: 1952-1972, undated.
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Committees, 1952-1972, undated; 3
  - Judiciary, 1952-1972, undated; 12
    - Civil Rights (1 of 2), 1965 (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Civil Rights (2 of 2), 1965 (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - Civil Rights, Names, A-C, 1966 (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - Civil Rights, Names, D-M, 1966 (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - Civil Rights, Names, N-Z, 1966 (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Civil Rights, 1967 (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - Civil Rights, Names, A-D, 1968 (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - Civil Rights, Names, E-P, 1968 (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - Civil Rights, Names, R-Z, 1968 (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - Civil Rights, 1971 (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - Civil Rights Act of 1963 (1 of 3) (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - Civil Rights Act of 1963 (2 of 3) (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - Civil Rights Act of 1963 (3 of 3) (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - Civil Rights, Constitutional Principles, 1956 (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - Civil Rights, Data, 1964 (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - Civil Rights, Dowdy’s Views of the Civil Rights Bill, 1966 (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - Civil Rights, Out of District, 1964 (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - Civil Rights, Racism Publications, 1957 (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - Civil Rights, Sex and Civil Rights, 1965 (Box 173, Folder 7)
    - Civil Rights, Speech by Congressman Dowdy, 1964 (Box 173, Folder 8)
    - Coin-Operated Phonographs, 1959 (Box 173, Folder 9)
    - Constitutional Convention, 1971 (Box 173, Folder 10)
    - Constitutional Precedence, 1962 (Box 173, Folder 11)
    - Copyright Laws, 1965-1971 (Box 173, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1953-1955 (Box 173, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 173, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1957-1958 (Box 174, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1957-1958 (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (1 of 3), 1961-1962 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (2 of 3), 1961-1962 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (3 of 3), 1961-1962 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 176, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Inter-Committee, 1957-1960 (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - Courts, Court of Claims, 1964 (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - Courts, Crime Control and Safe Streets Act, 1970 (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - Courts, Cyclamate and Indemnification Bill, 1970-1972 (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - Courts, Federal Courts, 1957 (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - Courts, Federal Courts and Judges, 1959-1967 (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - Courts, Juke Box, 1963 (Box 177, Folder 8)
    - Courts, National District Attorney’s Association, 1960 (Box 177, Folder 9)
    - Courts, Salaries of Judges, Attorneys, and Congressmen, 1952-1961 (Box 177, Folder 10)
    - Data, 1953-1959 (Box 177, Folder 11)
    - Data, 1959-1964 (Box 177, Folder 12)
    - Data, 1964-1971 (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - D.C. Transit Compact, Dowdy Speech, 1966 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - Elections, Election of President/Vice President, 1960-1972 (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - Elections, Election of President/Vice President Opinion Ballot, 1964 (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - Elections, U.S. Providing for the Election of President/Vice President?, 1959 (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - Equal Opportunity, Age Discrimination, 1957 (Box 178, Folder 6)
    - Equal Opportunity, Price Discrimination, 1956-1958 (Box 178, Folder 7)
    - Equal Opportunity, Senate Bill #11, 1956-1958 (Box 178, Folder 8)
    - Equal Rights Amendment, 1957-1972 (Box 178, Folder 9)
    - Equal Right for Men and Women, 1959 (Box 178, Folder 10)
    - Equal Rights for Women, 1961-1970 (Box 178, Folder 11)
    - Equal Rights for Women (1 of 2), 1971 (Box 178, Folder 12)
    - Equal Rights for Women (2 of 2), 1971 (Box 178, Folder 13)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), 1966 (Box 178, Folder 14)
    - Firearms, 1965-1966 (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - Firearms (1 of 8), 1968 (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - Firearms (2 of 8), 1968 (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - Firearms (3 of 8), 1968 (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - Firearms (4 of 8), 1968 (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - Firearms (5 of 8), 1968 (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - Firearms (6 of 8), 1968 (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - Firearms (7 of 8), 1968 (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - Firearms (8 of 8), 1968 (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - Firearms, Out of District, 1968 (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - Firearms, Names, A-C, 1968 (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - Firearms, Names, D-H, 1968 (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - Firearms, Names, I-N, 1968 (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - Firearms, Names, O-S, 1968 (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - Firearms, Names, T-Z, 1968 (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - Firearms, 1969-1970 (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - Firearms, 1971-1972 (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - Firearms Control, 1965-1967 (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - Firearms Control, 1967 (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - Firearms, NAR Data, 1967 (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - Firearms, Petitions, 1968 (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - Firearms, Federal Pistol Registration, 1962 (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - Firearms, Registration, 1963-1964 (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - Gun Control, 1972 (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - Hawaii, 1961 (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - Immigration and Naturalization, 1957-1962 (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - Immigration and Naturalization, 1963-1966 (Box 183, Folder 7)
    - Immigration and Naturalization, 1967-1970 (Box 183, Folder 8)
    - Immigration and Naturalization, 1971 (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - Immigration and Naturalization, 1972 (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - Impeachment, Judge Robert Tehan, 1970 (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - Impeachment, Supreme Court Justice Earl Warren, 1959-1961 (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - Impeachment, Supreme Court Justice Earl Warren (1 of 4), 1961 (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - Impeachment, Supreme Court Justice Earl Warren (2 of 4), 1961 (Box 184, Folder 6)
    - Impeachment, Supreme Court Justice Earl Warren (3 of 4), 1961 (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - Impeachment, Supreme Court Justice Earl Warren (4 of 4), 1961 (Box 185, Folder 2)
    - Impeachment, Supreme Court Justice William O’Douglas, 1970 (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - Obscenity (1 of 2), 1958 (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - Obscenity (2 of 2), 1958 (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - Obscenity, 1959-1960 (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - Obscenity, 1966-1969 (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - Obscenity, 1970-1972 (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - Obscenity, Anti-Obscenity Articles, 1957-1958 (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - Obscenity, Anti-Obscenity Mail from Texas, 1957-1958 (Box 186, Folder 5)
    - Obscenity, Anti-Pornography, 1972 (Box 186, Folder 6)
    - Obscenity, Articles, Editorials, Speeches, 1957-1959 (Box 186, Folder 7)
    - Obscenity, Crime Bill: Pornography, 1966 (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - Obscenity, Decency in the Mass Media, 1970 (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - Obscenity, Dissemination of Obscene Mail, 1958 (Box 187, Folder 3)
    - Obscenity, ImmortalityDLPornography, 1961 (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - Obscenity, Juvenile Delinquency, 1955 (Box 187, Folder 5)
    - Obscenity, Mail Obscenity, 1953-1957 (Box 187, Folder 6)
    - Obscenity, Mailing of Obscene Matter, 1957-1958 (Box 187, Folder 7)
    - Obscenity, Morally Offensive Mail Matter, 1963-1964 (Box 187, Folder 8)
    - Obscenity, Pamphlets, 1960 (Box 187, Folder 9)
    - Obscenity, Statutory Regulation of Obscenity, 1965 (Box 187, Folder 10)
    - Obscenity, Sample Publications, undated (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - Obscenity, Writ of Certiorari, 1957 (Box 188, Folder 2)
    - Parole Laws, 1972 (Box 188, Folder 3)
    - Patents, 1964-1970 (Box 188, Folder 4)
    - Petroleum Distribution Act, 1963 (Box 188, Folder 5)
    - Port of New York Authority Inquiry, 1960 (Box 188, Folder 6)
    - Private Communication Facilities, 1957-1961 (Box 188, Folder 7)
    - Publications, A Christian View on Segregation, 1954 (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - Publications, A Sickness in Society, undated (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - Publications, Automobile Currents and Countercurrents, 1971 (Box 189, Folder 3)
    - Publications, Blueprint for Total Federal Regimentation, 1964 (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - Publications, Church, State, and the Public Schools, 1963 (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - Publications, Civil Rights and Federal Powers, undated (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - Publications, Constitutional Emasculation Through Treaty Power, 1953 (Box 189, Folder 7)
    - Publications, Desegregation of Public Schools, 1967 (Box 189, Folder 8)
    - Publications, Integrated Education, 1967-1968 (Box 189, Folder 9)
    - Publications, Is It True What They Say About Dixie?, undated (Box 189, Folder 10)
    - Publications, iLegislative Analysis, 1961 (Box 189, Folder 11)
    - Publications, Nondiscrimination in Federally Assisted Programs, 1965 (Box 189, Folder 12)
    - Publications, Poison Peddling on America’s Boulevards, 1953 (Box 189, Folder 13)
    - Publications, Senate Joint Resolution 1, 1953 (Box 189, Folder 14)
    - Publications, State Taxation of Interstate Income: New Dimensions of an Old Problem, 1959 (Box 189, Folder 15)
    - Publications, State Taxation of Interstate Sales, 1960 (Box 189, Folder 16)
    - Publications, Statement of Views, 1953 (Box 189, Folder 17)
    - Publications, The Baylor Line, 1965 (Box 189, Folder 18)
    - Publications, The Church Looks at Immorality in Print and on Screen, 1959 (Box 189, Folder 19)
    - Publications, The Citizen, 1964 (Box 189, Folder 20)
    - Publications, The Dagger in Dixie’s Heart, undated (Box 189, Folder 21)
    - Publications, The Doctrine of Interposition, 1957 (Box 189, Folder 22)
    - Publications, The Plaquemine Story, undated (Box 189, Folder 23)
    - Publications, The Race Problem from the Standpoint of One Who is Concerned About the Evils of Miscegenation, 1955 (Box 189, Folder 24)
    - Publications, The Racial Issue, undated (Box 189, Folder 25)
    - Publications, The Supreme Court Decision on Bible Reading and Prayer, 1964 (Box 189, Folder 26)
    - Publications, The Truth, 1964 (Box 189, Folder 27)
    - Publications, The Ugly Truth About the NAACP, undated (Box 189, Folder 28)
    - Publications, The Unconstitutionality of the 14th Amendment, undated (Box 189, Folder 29)
    - Publications, These Men Believed, undated (Box 189, Folder 30)
    - Publications, Treaty Law, 1953 (Box 189, Folder 31)
    - Publications, Trickery, Treachery, Tyranny, and Treason in Washington, 1957 (Box 189, Folder 32)
    - Publications, UAW Women’s Resolution, 1970 (Box 189, Folder 33)
    - Publications, Unmaking the Civil Rights Bill, undated (Box 189, Folder 34)
    - Publications, Voting Rights on Trial in Oklahoma, 1966 (Box 189, Folder 35)
    - Publications, What the Motion Picture Theatres Mean to You and What You Can Do to Save Them, 1958 (Box 189, Folder 36)
    - Publications, Where Nixon Stands, 1963 (Box 189, Folder 37)
    - Publications, Why Kennedy Must Be Impeached!, 1962 (Box 189, Folder 38)
    - Segregation, 1954-1970 (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - Segregation, Southern Manifesto, 1956 (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - States’ Rights, 1957-1960 (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - States’ Rights, 1962-1963 (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - States’ Rights, Mississippi, 1962-1963 (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - States’ Rights, Protecting Moral Standards, 1959 (Box 190, Folder 6)
    - States’ Rights, Smith Bill, 1962 (Box 190, Folder 7)
    - State Taxation, 1961 (Box 190, Folder 8)
    - Teamsters Union, 1964 (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - Tidelands, 1951-1953 (Box 191, Folder 2)
    - Tidelands, Data, 1951-1954 (Box 191, Folder 3)
    - Treaties and Executive Agreements, Bricker Amendment Data, 1954 (Box 191, Folder 4)
    - Veterans, Catholic War Veterans, 1964 (Box 191, Folder 5)
    - Veterans, Congressional Charter to Veterans of WWI, 1957 (Box 191, Folder 6)
    - Veterans, H.R. 4412 WWI Charter Bill, 1957-1958 (Box 191, Folder 7)
    - Veterans, Jewish War Veterans, 1957 (Box 191, Folder 8)
    - Veterans, Paralyzed Veterans of America, 1965 (Box 191, Folder 9)
    - Veterans, Veteran’s Relief, 1957-1958 (Box 191, Folder 10)
    - Voting, 1965-1971 (Box 191, Folder 11)
    - Voting, Names, A-L, 1965 (Box 191, Folder 12)
    - Voting, Names, M-Z, 1965 (Box 192, Folder 1)
    - Voting, Mississippi Challenge, 1965 (Box 192, Folder 2)
    - Voting Age, 1968-1970 (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - Voting Rights Act of 1965, Documents (Box 192, Folder 4)
    - Voting Rights Act of 1965, Incoming Documents (Box 192, Folder 5)
  - Merchant Marines, 1953-1972; 13
    - Correspondence, 1953-1963 (Box 192, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1972 (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - Post Offices and Civil Service Commission, 1947-1972; 14
    - Civil Service Retirement, 1953-1955 (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - Civil Service Retirement (1 of 2), 1955-1956 (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - Civil Service Retirement (2 of 2), 1955-1956 (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - Civil Service Retirement, 1957-1962 (Box 193, Folder 4)
    - Civil Service Retirement Act, 1955 (Box 193, Folder 5)
    - Communist Propaganda in U.S. Mail, 1961-1962 (Box 193, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1953-1954 (Box 193, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1953-1954 (Box 193, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1955-1956 (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1955-1956 (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 195, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1970 (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1970 (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 195, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Inter-Committee, 1953-1956 (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - Data, 1947-1954 (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - Data, 1955-1960 (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - D.C. Correctional Department, 1955 (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - Fourth Class Post Offices, 1956 (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - Fraud, 1959 (Box 196, Folder 6)
    - H.R. 1939, 1953 (Box 196, Folder 7)
    - Longevity Benefits, 1961 (Box 196, Folder 8)
    - Parcel Post Relief Bill, 1956 (Box 196, Folder 9)
    - Pay Raise, 1953-1954 (Box 196, Folder 10)
    - Pay Raise (1 of 3), 1955 (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Pay Raise (2 of 3), 1955 (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Pay Raise (3 of 3), 1955 (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - Pay Raise, 1960-1962 (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - Pay Raise Mail from District, 1955-1956 (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - Pornography, 1953-1956 (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - Pornography, 1956-1959 (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - Post Office Data, 1955-1970 (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Postal Operations (1 of 2), 1955-1956 (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Postal Operations (2 of 2), 1955-1956 (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Postal Operations Sub-Committee (1 of 2), 1955-1956 (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Postal Pay Increase, 1957-1959 (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Postal Rate Increase, 1953-1954 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - Postal Rate Increase, 1956-1962 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Postal Rates, 1955-1958 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Public Law 199 (1 of 2), 1953 (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - Public Law 199 (2 of 2), 1953 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Publications, Better Federal Personnel Management, 1954 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Publications, Bill Analysis, 1957 (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - Publications, Catholic Men, 1956 (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - Publications, Concepts of Postal Economics (C.O.P.E.), 1970 (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - Publications, Good Government, 1953 (Box 199, Folder 9)
    - Publications, Obscenity, Pornography, and Common Sense, 1964 (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - Publications, Postal Employees’ Bonds, 1955 (Box 199, Folder 11)
    - Publications, Proposals for Reduction of the Postal Deficit, 1953 (Box 199, Folder 12)
    - Publications, Report on Audit of the Postal Savings System, 1954 (Box 199, Folder 13)
    - Publications, Retirement Life, 1955 (Box 199, Folder 14)
    - Publications, Southern States Industrial Council (SSIC) Bulletin, 1970 (Box 199, Folder 15)
    - Publications, The American Federationist, 1953 (Box 199, Folder 16)
    - Publications, The Railroad Passenger Deficit Problem, 1955 (Box 199, Folder 17)
    - Publications, The Reorganization of the U.S. Civil Service Commission, 1953 (Box 199, Folder 18)
    - Publications, The Union Postal Clerk, 1954 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Richmond Post Office, 1953 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Salary for Classified Employees, 1955 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Union Recognition to Federal Employees, 1956 (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - Weight and Size Limitations, 1954 (Box 200, Folder 5)
  - Public Works, 1953-1972; 15
    - Brazos River Authority, 1953-1958 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Colorado River Project, 1961 (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - Corps of Engineers, 1953 (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1954-1963 (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 200, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1972 (Box 200, Folder 11)
    - Economic Development, 1965 (Box 200, Folder 12)
    - H.R. 12253, Lake McAlister, 1960 (Box 200, Folder 13)
    - Highways, 1953-1954 (Box 200, Folder 14)
    - Highways (1 of 2), 1956 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Highways (2 of 2), 1956 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Highways, 1957-1963 (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Highway Project, 1955 (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - McGee Bend Dam, 1953 (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Niagara Power Project, 1957 (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Publications, Bill Analysis, 1957 (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - Rivers and Harbors, 1967 (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - Rivers and Harbors Flood Control, 1966 (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - St. Lawrence Seaway Project, 1953-1954 (Box 201, Folder 10)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1957-1959 (Box 201, Folder 11)
    - Trinity River, 1958-1961 (Box 201, Folder 12)
    - Trinity River, Soil Conservation, 1953 (Box 201, Folder 13)
    - Water Pollution, 1961 (Box 201, Folder 14)
  - Rules, 1953-1972; 16
    - Correspondence, 1953-1960 (Box 201, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence (1 of 3), 1961 (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (2 of 3), 1961 (Box 202, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (3 of 3), 1961 (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1962-1972 (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - Publications, How Should We Elect the President?, 1969 (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - Publications, Legislative Analysis, 1969 (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - Publications, The American Legion, 1966 (Box 202, Folder 7)
  - Science and Technology, 1959-1971; 17
    - Science and Technology, 1959-1971 (Box 202, Folder 8)
  - Small Business, 1953-1971, undated; 18
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1953-1971 (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1953-1971 (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - Publications, Bill Analysis, 1957 (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - Publications, Lone Star News, undated (Box 203, Folder 4)
  - Un-American Activities, 1953-1965, undated; 19
    - Anti-Communism, 1962 (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Communist Propaganda, 1962 (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1953-1959 (Box 203, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1960 (Box 203, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1960 (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - Data, 1961 (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Opinion Ballot, 1964 (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - Publications, Brainwashing, undated (Box 204, Folder 7)
    - Publications, Rules of Procedure, 1953, 1961 (Box 204, Folder 8)
    - Publications, This is the A.D.L., Mr. Hoover!, 1958 (Box 204, Folder 9)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1953-1972; 20
    - Correspondence, 1953-1956 (Box 204, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Data, 1953-1956 (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - Data, 1957-1961 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Data, 1962-1972 (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - Opinion Ballots, 1963 (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - Pensions of WWII Vets, 1960 (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - Publications, Medal of Honor Roster, 1971 (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - Publications, VA Fact Sheets, 1956 (Box 206, Folder 6)
  - Ways and Means, 1953-1972; 21
    - Correspondence, 1953-1956 (Box 206, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 206, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1963-1972 (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Medicare, 1960-1961 (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Medicare (1 of 3), 1965 (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Medicare (2 of 3), 1965 (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Medicare (3 of 3), 1965 (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Medicare, 1966-1967 (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Medicare, 1968 (Box 208, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Medicare, 1970-1971 (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - Data, Medicare, 1965 (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - Documents, Medicare, 1965 (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Implementation Pt. 1, Medicare, 1966 (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - Implementation Pt. 2, Medicare, 1966 (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - King-Anderson, Medicare (1 of 3), 1962 (Box 209, Folder 6)
    - King-Anderson, Medicare (2 of 3), 1962 (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - King-Anderson, Medicare (3 of 3), 1962 (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - King-Anderson, Medicare, 1963-1964 (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - King-Anderson, Medicare, 1964-1965 (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - Profit Sharing, 1972 (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - Publications, Legislative Analysis, 1968 (Box 210, Folder 6)
    - Publications, Legislative Research, 1963 (Box 210, Folder 7)
    - Publications, Rail Cars for Progress and Defense, 1957 (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - Publications, Social Security, 1954 (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - Publications, The Trade Expansion Act of 1962 (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - Revenue Sharing, 1972 (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - Social Security, 1953-1955 (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - Social Security, 1956-1959 (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - Social Security, 1960-1961 (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - Social Security, 1962-1963 (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - Social Security, 1964-1972 (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - Social Security Amendments of 1960 (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - Social Security Amendments of 1965 (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Social Security Amendments of 1969 (Box 212, Folder 5)
    - Social Security, Elder Care Act of 1965 (Box 212, Folder 6)
    - Social Security, Family Assistance Act, 1970 (Box 212, Folder 7)
    - Social Security, Hospital Insurance, Social Security, and Public Assistance, 1965 (Box 212, Folder 8)
    - Social Security, Letters from District (1 of 2), 1954 (Box 213, Folder 1)
    - Social Security, Letters from District (2 of 2), 1954 (Box 213, Folder 2)
    - Taxes, 1953 (Box 213, Folder 3)
    - Taxes, 1954 (Box 213, Folder 4)
    - Taxes, 1955-1956 (Box 213, Folder 5)
    - Taxes, 1957-1958 (Box 213, Folder 6)
    - Taxes, 1959 (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - Taxes, 1960 (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - Taxes (1 of 2), 1961 (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - Taxes (2 of 2), 1961 (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - Taxes (1 of 2), 1962 (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - Taxes (2 of 2), 1962 (Box 214, Folder 6)
    - Taxes (1 of 2), 1963 (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - Taxes (2 of 2), 1963 (Box 215, Folder 2)
    - Taxes, 1964-1972 (Box 215, Folder 3)
    - Tax Act of 1930, 1958 (Box 215, Folder 4)
    - Taxes, Beef Imports, Opinion Ballots, 1964 (Box 215, Folder 5)
    - Taxes, Beef Industry, 1964 (Box 215, Folder 6)
    - Taxes, Data, 1959 (Box 215, Folder 7)
    - Taxes, Excise Tax Reduction, 1965 (Box 216, Folder 1)